*   English  
    
      Deutsch  English

Hero Forge® Privacy Policy
==========================

Effective Date: This Privacy Policy is effective and was last updated as of January 1, 2023.

Introduction
------------

Sky Castle Studios, LLC (“Sky Castle,” "Company" or "We") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit HeroForge.com or one of our other websites, applications or other services from Company (each referred to herein as a “Site” and collectively, the “Sites”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

**NOTICE: THIS PRIVACY POLICY CONTAINS A MANDATORY ARBITRATION AGREEMENT. YOU AGREE THAT ANY CLAIMS YOU MAY HAVE AGAINST US RELATING TO THE SITE OR THE SERVICES, THIS PRIVACY POLICY OR ANY TERMS AND CONDITIONS CONTAINED HEREIN MUST BE ARBITRATED, AND YOU EXPRESSLY WAIVE THE RIGHT TO (1) ASSERT CLAIMS AGAINST US IN COURT; (2) PARTICIPATE IN A REPRESENTATIVE OR CLASS ACTION; AND (3) HAVE A JURY HEAR YOUR CASE. YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO HAVE ALL OF YOUR CLAIMS ARBITRATED ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS ONLY. YOU ALSO AGREE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND BY OUR TERMS AND CONDTIONS.**

This policy applies to information we collect:

* On the Site(s).
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and the Sites.
* Through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Site, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and the Site.
* When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

It does not apply to information collected by:

* Us offline or through any means other than through a Site; or
* Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or through the Sites.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Sites. By accessing or using the Sites, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Sites after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

Children
--------

The Sites are not directed to children under the age of sixteen (16). If you are under sixteen (16), do not provide your Personal Information on or to the Site. We do not knowingly collect on the Site any Personal Information from children under sixteen (16). Users outside of the United States who are below the age of eighteen (18) (or the age of the majority in the applicable jurisdiction) should not use the Site without authorization from a parent or legal guardian. If a parent or guardian becomes aware of his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, please contact us at: [\[email protected\]](https://www.heroforge.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). California residents under 16 years of age may have additional rights regarding the collection and sale of their personal information. Please see Your State Privacy Rights for more information.

Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It
------------------------------------------------------

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Sites, including information:

* By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, email address, telephone number, and any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (**"personal information"**);
* That is about you but individually does not identify you, such as your public profile nickname, or IP address; and/or
* About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Site, and usage details.

We collect this information:

* Directly from you when you provide it to us.
* Automatically as you navigate through the Site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.
* From third parties, for example, our business partners.

_Information You Provide to Us_

The information we collect on or through our Sites may include:

* Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Sites. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Site, subscribing to our service, posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Sites.
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses) if you contact us.
* Your responses to surveys, questionnaires, or forms that we might ask you to complete.
* Details of transactions you carry out through our Sites and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through or subscribing to our Sites.
* Your search queries on the Sites.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, **"posted"**) on public areas of the Sites, or transmitted to other users of the Sites or third parties (collectively, **"User Contributions"**). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Sites with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

_Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies_

As you navigate through and interact with our Site, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

* Details of your visits to our Sites, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Sites.
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking).

The information we collect automatically is only statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Site according to your individual interests.
* Speed up your searches.
* Recognize you when you return to our Site.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Sites. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Sites.
* **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Sites and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
----------------------------------------------------------

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Sites are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies \[alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies\] to collect information about you when you use our Sites. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

* To present our Site and its contents to you.
* To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
* To provide you with notices about your account/subscription, including expiration and renewal notices./li>
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
* To notify you about changes to our Sites or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
* To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Sites.
* To fulfill requests for services.
* To protect the security or integrity of the Sites and our business.
* To share your Personal Information with third parties for our marketing, commercial and advertising purposes, subject to any opt-out rights you may have.
* To optimize and refine the Site
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
* For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties' goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please adjust your user preferences in your account profile. For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers' target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

Disclosure of Your Information
------------------------------

* To data partners for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.
* To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Sky Castle Studios, LLC’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Sky Castle Studios, LLC about our Site’s users is among the assets transferred.
* To auditors and professional advisers like bankers, lawyers, accountants and insurers.
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
* With your consent.
* When you contribute to a social, community or other publicly available area or feature of the Sites, the information and content that you post may be made available to the general public, depending on your settings (which is why we recommend that you do not submit or post any sensitive personal information, such as your full name, home address, phone number or other information that would enable others to contact or locate you).
* With our advertising and marketing vendors for our own marketing purposes.

We may also disclose your personal information:

* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
* To enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions \[[https://www.heroforge.com/ToS](https://www.heroforge.com/ToS)\] and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information
------------------------------------------------------

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

* **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
* **Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising.** We do not share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for their own promotional purposes.
* **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your email address used by the Company to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt-out by logging into the Site and adjusting your newsletter preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may click the “unsubscribe” button to be omitted from future email distributions.

We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (**"NAI"**) on the NAI's website.

Accessing and Correcting Your Information
-----------------------------------------

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Site and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.heroforge.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Site, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Site users.

**Residents of certain states, such as California, Nevada, Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia, and Utah may have additional personal information rights and choices.**

Your State Privacy Rights
-------------------------

If you are a California, Nevada, Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia, or Utah resident, your state's laws may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit our Privacy Policy for California Residents \[[https://www.heroforge.com/Privacy/California](https://www.heroforge.com/Privacy/California)\].

Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia and Utah each provide their state residents with rights to:

* Confirm whether we process their personal information.
* Access and delete certain personal information.
* Data portability.
* Opt-out of personal data processing for targeted advertising and sales.

Colorado, Connecticut and Virginia also provide their state residents with rights to:

* Correct inaccuracies in their personal information, taking into account the information's nature processing purpose.
* Opt-out of profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects.

To exercise any of these rights please check the appropriate box available through your account or email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.heroforge.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Nevada provides its residents with a limited right to opt-out of certain personal information sales. However, please know we do not currently sell data triggering that statute's opt-out requirements.

GDPR and UK Rights
------------------

If you are a resident of the European Union or the United Kingdom, EU or UK laws may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your these rights, visit [https://www.heroforge.com/Privacy/GDPR](https://www.heroforge.com/Privacy/GDPR)

Data Security
-------------

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls.

We do not currently collect financial information, as that information is collected and stored by our third party payment processor. However, we may from time to time request and receive some of your financial information from our payment processor or from you for the purposes of completing transactions you have initiated, protecting against or identifying possibly fraudulent transactions, and as otherwise needed to manage our business.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Sites. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Sites.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Sites. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Sites.

To use certain aspects of our services, such as making a purchase or subscribing we may require credit or debit card account information. By submitting your credit or debit card account information through the Services, you expressly consent to the sharing of your information with third party merchants, subscription and billing processors, and payment processors. These third parties may store your credit or debit card account information so you can use our Services in the future. We do not have your complete credit or debit card account information, store your credit or debit card account information, or have direct control over or responsibility for your credit or debit card account information. While we require that such third party merchants, billing processors, and payment processors use reasonable procedures to help protect your credit or debit card information, we cannot guarantee that transmissions of your credit or debit card account information or Personal Information will always be secure or that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat the security measures taken by us or our third-party service providers. We assume no liability or responsibility for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access, or other causes beyond our control.

Governing Law/Dispute Resolution/Arbitration
--------------------------------------------

All matters relating to the Site and this privacy Policy and any dispute or claim arising therefrom or related thereto (in each case, including non-contractual disputes or claims), shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the internal laws of the State of California without giving effect to any choice or conflict of law provision or rule (whether of the State of California or any other jurisdiction).

By using the Site you agree that any dispute, claim or controversy arising out of or relating to this privacy policy or the breach, termination, enforcement, interpretation or validity thereof, including the determination of the scope or applicability of this agreement to arbitrate, shall be determined by arbitration in Los Angeles, California before a single neutral arbitrator. The arbitration shall be administered by Judicial Arbitration and Mediation Services, Inc. (“JAMS”) pursuant to its Comprehensive Arbitration Rules and Procedures. The parties to arbitration may use legal counsel at their own expense. All costs of arbitration (including arbitrator fees) shall be paid by Sky Castle, except only that if you bring the arbitration, you may be charged an initial filing fee that shall not exceed the filing fees that you would incur for bringing an action in court. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, in the event that any party seeks injunctive or equitable relief with respect to any actual or threatened breach of this privacy policy, or with respect to public injunctive relief, such party may seek relief in a court of competent jurisdiction. Notwithstanding anything else in this privacy policy or the JAMS rules, any parties subject to this arbitration provision shall be barred from bringing or participating in any Class Action (as defined below) related to a dispute covered by this arbitration provision. **Notwithstanding anything else in this privacy policy or the JAMS rules, it is agreed that the arbitrator is specifically denied the authority to consider or certify any Class Action under this privacy policy.** However, if these Class Action restrictions are ever deemed illegal or unenforceable, they shall be severed from this arbitration provision. In that event, any Class Action shall by exempted from this arbitration provision and brought in court of competent jurisdiction, in connection therewith and each of the parties consent to the sole and exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts of the State of California, County of Los Angeles, Central District. For purposes of this privacy policy, the term “Class Action” shall mean claims brought on behalf of or allegedly representing or including other persons or entities, including but not limited to any class, consolidated, representative, collective or private attorney general action. This arbitration provision is subject to the Federal Arbitration Act, and may be enforced in any court of competent jurisdiction.

**WAIVER. BY AGREEING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICYAND SUBJECT THERETO, YOU HEREBY IRREVOCABLY WAIVE ANY RIGHT YOU MAY HAVE TO A COURT TRIAL (OTHER THAN SMALL CLAIMS COURT AS PROVIDED ABOVE) OR TO SERVE AS A REPRESENTATIVE, AS A PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL, OR IN ANY OTHER REPRESENTATIVE CAPACITY, OR TO PARTICIPATE AS A MEMBER OF A CLASS OF CLAIMANTS, IN ANY LAWSUIT, ARBITRATION OR OTHER PROCEEDING FILED AGAINST US AND/OR RELATED THIRD PARTIES.**

Changes to Our Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address specified in your account. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Site and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

Contact Information
-------------------

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.heroforge.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).
